Guide to the Communist Party of the United States of America Audio Collection TAM.132.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series II: Reel-to-Reel Audio Tapes: Public Events, 1920s - 1984
  - Subseries II:A: Events
    - Hiroshima Day. Includes William Gropper(?) [CPA #318], [Aug 6], 1971 (Box 17, Folder 132_0534)
    - Government Workers Rally / OBA Convention [CPA #313], Aug 15, 1971; Apr 1971 (Box 18, Folder 132_0535)
    - Gus Hall, "The Economy." Master A [CPA #837], Sep 1971 (Box 18, Folder 132_0536)
    - Henry Winston on Chile and Imperialism / Gus Hall on the Economy [CPA #265], Sep 1, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 132_0537)
    - William Patterson, 80th Birthday. Chicago, IL [CPA #954], Oct 22, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 132_0538)
    - Attica Rally / William Patterson, Birthday / 3rd Unitarian Church Community Sunday [CPA #317], Oct 26, 1971; Oct 31, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 132_0539)
    - Peace Rally. Chicago, IL / Chicago Council, National Association for American-Soviet Friendship [CPA #337], Nov 6, 1971; Nov 7, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 132_0540)
    - Bobby Seale / Victor Perlo [CPA #813], Dec 4, 1971; Dec 1971 (Box 18, Folder 132_0541)
    - Harlow. Blue Angel. Nixon. Fania Davis on Stan Dote. Madam Binh. [Shirley] Chisholm. Nixon. Franklin Alexander on Angela Davis' Victory [CPA #851], 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0542)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 1.1 [CPA #766], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0543)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 1.2 [CPA #765], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0544)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 2 [CPA #767], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0545)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 2 [CPA #768], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0546)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Includes Dennis Mora. Tape 3. [CPA #761], 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0547)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 3.1 [CPA #763], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0548)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 3.2 [CPA #769], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0549)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 4 [CPA #764], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0550)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 5 [CPA #762], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0551)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Rally. Tape 6 [CPA #770], [1972] (Box 18, Folder 132_0552)
    - Press Conference. Henry Winston, on Angela Davis (before posting bail). [CPA #462], Jan 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0553)
    - Press Conference. Includes Gus Hall, Ishmael Flory [CPA #580], Jan 31, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0554)
    - Daily World International Women's Day Event. Includes Angela Davis, Ruby Dee [CPA #465], Mar 10, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0555)
    - Anti-Bombing Rally. Logan Monument, Grant Park, Chicago, IL / Anti-Bombing Rally. Includes Fania Davis. Antioch College, Yellow Springs, OH. [CPA #352], Apr 20, 1972; May 4, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0556)
    - Angela Davis. Chicago, IL. Tape 1 [CPA #617], Jun 16, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0557)
    - Angela Davis. Chicago, IL. Tape 2 [CPA #618], Jun 16, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0558)
    - Angela Davis. Chicago, IL and Detroit, MI / Gus Hall. Chicago, IL [CPA #858], Jun 16, 1972; Jun 18, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0559)
    - Trade Unionists for Action and Democracy (TUAD) Election Conference [CPA #416], Jul 1, 1972 (Box 12, Reel 132_0373)
    - Gus Hall, Speech. "Anthony" Answers Hall, Duluth, MN [CPA #807], Aug 11, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0560)
    - Conference on Pan Africanism. Tape 1 of 9 [CPA #642], Sep 11, 1972 (Box 10, Reel 132_0306)
    - Conference on Pan Africanism. Tape 2 of 9 [CPA #643], Sep 11, 1972 (Box 10, Reel 132_0307)
    - Racism and Chauvinism. Includes Henry Winston and Irving Potash [CPA #638], Oct 4, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0561)
    - Jane Fonda / OBA Convention [CPA #623], Oct 19, 1972; Oct 14, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 132_0562)
    - Bill Scott, Quality of Life in Auto Plants [CPA #622], 1973 (Box 18, Folder 132_0563)
    - 29th Ward Peoples Convention. Chicago, IL. [CPA #327], Feb 10, 1973 (Box 10, Reel 132_0292)
    - Political Prisoners Conference, Chicago, IL / De Mau Mau Rally [CPA #321], Feb 17, 1973; Feb 24, 1973 (Box 11, Reel 132_0346)
    - Alva Buxenbaum. [CPA #967], Mar 20, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 132_0564)
    - Political Prisoners Founding Conference Rally [CPA #326], May 12, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 132_0565)
    - Political Prisoners Founding Conference. Opening Plenary. Chicago, IL. Tape 1 [CPA #322], May 12, 1973 (Box 11, Reel 132_0344)
    - Political Prisoners Founding Conference, Chicago, IL. Opening Plenary. Tape 2 [CPA #354], May 13, 1973 (Box 11, Reel 132_0345)
    - Angela Davis [CPA #616], May 14, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 132_0566, Box 64, Cd 566 (disks 1-2))
    - Gus Hall, on the Economy. Master B [CPA #810], Sep 1973 (Box 18, Folder 132_0567)
    - Gus Hall, on Watergate and Ray Brezhnev. Master 1 [CPA #808], Jun 30(?), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0568)
    - Gus Hall on Watergate and Ray Brezhnev. Master 2 [CPA #809], Jun 30(?), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0569)
    - Gus Hall, on Watergate and Ray Brezhnev (?). Chicago, IL [CPA #795], Jun 30, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0570)
    - Press Conference, on Chile. Los Angeles Press Club, Los Angeles, CA. [CPA #268], Jul 14, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0571)
    - Chile Interview at Stadium. Santiago, Chile. Pablo Neruda's Funeral [CPA #270], Sep 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0572)
    - Henry Winston. "A" Master [CPA #789], Sep 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0573)
    - Henry Winston. "B" Master [CPA #787], Sep 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0574)
    - Chile Rally. Includes Angela Davis and Fred Halstead [CPA #264], Oct 13, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0575)
    - Anti Imperialist Conference on African Solidarity [CPA #415], Oct 17, 1973 (Box 10, Reel 132_0300)
    - Memorial Meeting for Salvador Allende. DePaul University, Chicago, IL. [CPA #269], Dec 11, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 132_0576)
    - Homage to [Salvador] Allende. Internazionale Singers (Italian) [CPA #1019], [circa 1973-1979?] (Box 19, Folder 132_0577)
    - Ishmael Flory, Political Campaign. Chicago, IL. [CPA #405], 1974 (Box 19, Folder 132_0578)
    - Inflation Rally / Operation PUSH (People United to Save Humanity) Rally [CPA #368], 1974; 1975 (Box 19, Folder 132_0579)
    - Chile Anniversary. Expo Cuba-Chile. 1973 Coup d'etat [CPA #263], Sep 1974 (Box 19, Folder 132_0580)
    - Communist Party, USA. Election Rally [CPA #363], Oct 1974 (Box 19, Folder 132_0581)
    - Ernest DeMaio, Tribute [CPA #825], Mar 8, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 132_0582)
    - Ernest DeMaio, Tribute. Edit Transfer 1 [CPA #824], [Mar 8, 1975] (Box 19, Folder 132_0583)
    - Ernest DeMaio, Tribute. Edit Transfer 2 [CPA #492], [Mar 8, 1975] (Box 19, Folder 132_0584)
    - Black Liberation Commission, National Anti-Imperialist Movement in Solidarity with African Liberation [CPA #865], Apr 11, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 132_0585)
    - Felt Forum Rally, New York, NY. Tape 2 [CPA #490], [1976] (Box 19, Folder 132_0586)
    - Henry Winston. Chicago [CPA #786], 1976 (Box 19, Folder 132_0587)
    - Press Conference. New York, NY [CPA #260], Jan 10, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 132_0588)
    - Gus Hall, Interview [CPA #924], Jun 8, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 132_0589)
    - Manhattan Center Rally. Includes Grace Mora [CPA #306], Jun 13, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 132_0590)
    - Gus Hall on Youth. Hall-Tyner, Ishmael Flory Campaign [CPA #806], Jul 16, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 132_0591)
    - Hyman Lumar, Memorial Service [CPA #624], Jul 19, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 132_0592)
    - Hosea Hudson, Jun 7, 1978 (Box 14, Reel 132_4992)
    - Paul Robeson, Youth Salute. Includes David Amram, Hazel Dickens, Odetta, John Randolph. Felt Forum, New York, NY. Tape 1 [CPA #899], Dec 16, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 132_0593)
    - Paul Robeson: Youth Salute. Felt Forum, New York, NY. Tape 2 [CPA #900], Dec 16, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 132_0594)
    - Gus Hall, on China [CPA #799], Mar 30, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 132_0595)
    - Hall - Davis Campaign Committee. "People before Profits" [CPA #839], [1980/1984] (Box 19, Folder 132_0596)
    - People's Inquest [CPA #939], Mar 1980 (Box 19, Folder 132_0597)
    - May Day, Union Square [CPA #393], May 3, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 132_0598)
    - People before Profits Rally. City College of New York, New York, NY. Tape 1 [CPA #488], Oct 19, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 132_0599)
    - People before Profits Rally. City College of New York, New York, NY. Includes Angela Davis. Tape 2 [CPA #413], Oct 19, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 132_0600)
    - Henry Winston, 62nd Anniversary of CPUSA. On Reaganism. [CPA #870], 1981 (Box 20, Folder 132_0601)
    - James Jackson [CPA #828], May 1981 (Box 20, Folder 132_0602)
    - Gus Hall, Reagan Ripoff [CPA #878], Jul 17, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 132_0603)
    - Karl Marx Centenary Conference. [Includes Timor Timofeyev]. Unity Center, New York, NY. Tape 1. [CPA #747], Mar 29, 1983 (Box 11, Reel 132_0329)
    - Karl Marx Centenary Conference. Unity Center, New York, NY. Tape 2 [CPA #745], Mar 29, 1983 (Box 11, Reel 132_0330)
    - Karl Marx Centenary Conference. [Includes Moses Mabhida]. Unity Center, New York, NY. Tape 3 [CPA #746], Mar 29, 1983 (Box 11, Reel 132_0331)
    - Gus Hall Speech, The 1984 Elections [CPA #833], Oct 16, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 132_0604)
    - AFL-CIO Solidarity Day. Includes Bayard Rustin. Washington, DC. Tape 1 [CPA #482], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0605)
    - AFL-CIO Solidarity Day. Includes Jessica Smith (Executive Director, Frontlash). Washington, DC. Tape 2 [CPA #959], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0606)
    - Angela Davis. Pittsburgh [CPA #], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0607)
    - Ben Davis (?) (recorded on slow speed) [CPA #640], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0608)
    - Ben Dobbs, Report [CPA #551], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0609)
    - Claude Lightfoot, Lecture. Leipzig University, East Germany. [CPA #871], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0610)
    - Claude Lightfoot, Speech [CPA #843], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0611)
    - Claude Lightfoot, Speech [CPA #861], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0612, Box 64, Cd 612 (disks 1-2))
    - Common People [CPA #792], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0613)
    - Conspiracy Trial. Aaron [CPA #414], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0614)
    - Daniel Rubin, Lenin and the Revolutionary Party [CPA #863], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0615)
    - De Mau Mau Defense Rally. Chicago, IL [CPA #418], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0616)
    - Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, Trip to Socialist Countries [CPA #869], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0617)
    - Fiorello LaGuardia. [CPA #759], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0618)
    - Gaynor Memorial [CPA #315], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0619)
    - Gus Hall, Casper Citron Interview [CPA #804], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0620)
    - Gus Hall on China in the 1960s (incomplete) [CPA #798], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0621)
    - Gus Hall, Interview [CPA #925], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0622)
    - Gus Hall, Put a Worker in the White House (incomplete) [CPA #829], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0623)
    - Gus Hall, Report to School [CPA #797], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0624)
    - Gus Hall, Speech. New York Marxist (?) School [Brecht Forum]. Tape 1 [CPA #831], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0625)
    - Political Affairs Forum. Gus Hall, Speech on Working Class Unity and Class Consciousness. [CPA #835], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0626)
    - Gus Hall, Summary [CPA #805], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0627)
    - Henry Winston, Black Youth and Anti-Imperialist Solidarity with the African Liberation Movements [CPA #868], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0628)
    - Henry Winston [possibly discussing United Automobile Workers] [CPA #819], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0629)
    - Henry Winston, Speech [CPA #1005], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0630)
    - Herbert Aptheker [CPA #760], undated (Box 20, Folder 132_0631)
    - Hosea Hudson, Memoirs. Tape 6 [CPA #849], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0632)
    - Huey Newton, Message to Sisters [CPA #817], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0633)
    - Hyman Lumer. Gosmar College [CPA #625], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0634)
    - James Jackson on Regis Debray book, Debray's thesis [CPA #483], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0635)
    - Jewish Racism [CPA #780], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0636)
    - John Howard Lawson, Re-recording [CPA #979], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0637)
    - Joseph North and Gaylord C. Leroy (Communist literary critic) [CPA #790], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0638)
    - Keynote Speech. Tape 1 [CPA #873], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0639)
    - Keynote Speech. Tape 2 [CPA #874], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0640)
    - Keynote Speech. Tape 3 [CPA #875], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0641)
    - Keynote Speech. Tape 4 [CPA #876], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0642)
    - Mark Lane on Oswald [CPA #845], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0643)
    - Marxism and Sex [CPA #782], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0644)
    - Mike Gold, on Malcolm Cowley and the 1930s. Includes Joe North. [CPA #933], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0645)
    - People before Profits (2?) [CPA #860], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0646)
    - People before Profits. Tape 2 [CPA #844], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0647)
    - Press Conference. Gus Hall on FBI and Levine. Duplicate #2 [CPA #558], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0648)
    - Press Conference. Gus Hall on Return from World Tour [CPA #596], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0649)
    - Simon Gerson [CPA #486], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0650)
    - Statements by Black American Heroes Who Liberated Themselves from the American Imperialist Army [CPA #850], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0651)
    - Unemployment Conference. Tape 3. [Includes Lou Weinstock] [CPA #367], undated (Box 12, Reel 132_0377)
    - Unemployment Conference. Tape 4 [CPA #502], undated (Box 12, Reel 132_0378)
    - Unidentified Public Event. Tape 2 of 3. [CPA #966], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0652)
    - Unidentified Public Event. Tape (?) of 3. [CPA #964], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0653)
    - Unidentified Public Event. Tape (?) of 3. [CPA #965], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0654)
    - Unidentified Speech 2, 1/65(?) [CPA #848], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0655)
    - Unidentified Speech. Tape 1 [CPA #1003], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0656)
    - Unidentified Speech. Tape 2 [CPA #960], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0657)
    - Unidentified Speech. Tape 3 [CPA #1007], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0658)
    - United Automobile Workers on Deerfield [CPA #820], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0659)
    - 5th Anniversary (?). Program includes witnesses from Reds (motion picture), including Hugo Gellert, Art Shields, Jessica Smith, William Weinstone. Unity Center, New York, NY. [CPA #487], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0660)
    - Wayne Morse (U.S. Senator) on Middle East. Eisenhower. Faubus on Little Rock [CPA #862], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0661)
    - W. E. B. Du Bois: Autobiographical Remarks [CPA #785], undated (Box 21, Folder 132_0662)
    - Youth Convention [CPA #251], Feb 9 (Box 9, Reel 132_0284)
    - Youth Convention [CPA #255], Feb 9 (Box 9, Reel 132_0285)
    - Youth Shop Conference [CPA #308], undated (Box 9, Reel 132_0289)
  - Subseries II:B: Radio and Television
    - Face the Nation. Interview with Nikita S. Khrushchev [CPA #24], Jun 2, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 132_0663)
    - Harry Bridges (President of the International Longshore and Warehouse Union), Interview with Mike Wallace [CPA #930], Aug 18, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 132_0664)
    - KPFK. Elizabeth Gurley Flynn, Interview with Art Wadsworth. Portrait of a Dedicated Woman. Los Angeles, CA. Broadcast 1/31/62 [CPA #22], Dec 5, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 132_0665)
    - WBBM-CBS. Gus Hall, Interview. Chicago, IL. [CPA #35], Dec 6, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 132_0666)
    - TASS (Moscow TV). Gus Hall, Interview. [CPA #1], Apr 8, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 132_0667)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr., Interview with J. McGwin/Studs Terkel. Chicago, IL. [CPA #14], Jul 1966 (Box 22, Folder 132_0668)
    - Middle East [CPA #29], [1967] (Box 22, Folder 132_0669)
    - Gus Hall, Interview on Return from Soviet Union's 50th Anniversary [CPA #926], [Sep 27, 1967] (Box 22, Folder 132_0670)
    - WXUR. Gus Hall, Interview. [CPA #568], Jan 29, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 132_0671)
    - Red Tape #16: Interview with Bobby Seale [CPA #32], Nov 1969 (Box 22, Folder 132_0672)
    - KMHL. Betty Smith (CP Candidate for State Auditor). Marshall, MN. [CPA #21], 1970 (Box 22, Folder 132_0673)
    - People's Inquest. First Edit. Includes Doc [Jack?] Stachel [CPA #419], Mar 8, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 132_0674)
    - Law & Law & Order [sic]. Forum, Includes Frank Donner (United Electrical Workers), W. Hayward Burns (National Conference of Black Lawyers), Paul Chevinier (ACLU Attorney), Mary Kaufman (National Lawyers Guild, Mass Defense Office). Aired 2/25/71. Center for Marxist Education, New York, NY. Tape 1 of 2. [CPA #484], Nov 13, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 132_0675)
    - [Law & Law & Order [sic]: Forum, Includes Frank Donner (United Electrical Workers), W. Hayward Burns (National Conference of Black Lawyers), Paul Chevinier (ACLU Attorney), Mary Kaufman (National Lawyers Guild, Mass Defense Office). [Aired 2/25/71]. Held at the Center for Marxist Education, New York NY. Tape 2 of 2. [CPA #479], Nov 13, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 132_0676)
    - Huey Newton on David Frost, 4/71 / Poindexter (track reversed), 5/71 [CPA #818], Apr 1971; May 1971 (Box 22, Folder 132_0677)
    - Election Spots [CPA #249], [1972] (Box 22, Folder 132_0678)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Campaign (14 min.) [CPA #921], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0679)
    - WQXR. Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Campaign Committee. Jarvis Tyner, Speaker. New York, NY (13 min. 25 sec.) [CPA #158], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0680)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Election Campaign. MI. Four 60-sec. spots 1 [CPA #199], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0681)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Election Campaign. MI. Four 60-sec. spots 2 [CPA #200], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0682)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Election Campaign Committee [CPA #192], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0683)
    - Gus Hall, Jarvis Tyner, and Herbert Aptheker (26 sec.) [CPA #202], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0684)
    - Gus Hall, Jarvis Tyner, and Herbert Aptheker Rally 2: Promo Spot (1 min.) [CPA #174], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0685)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Election Campaign. Spots (60 sec.) [CPA #146], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0686)
    - Gus Hall - Jarvis Tyner Election Campaign Videotape, Copy of Master (29 min.); Hall - Tyner Radio show (14 min.); Hall - Tyner Radio Show (4 min.); Radio Spots for Hall - Tyner (60 sec.). Two 60-sec. spots, Philadelphia Rally [CPA #145], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0687)
    - Gus Hall and Jarvis Tyner. Communist Party. #500 [CPA #100], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0688)
    - Gus Hall and Jarvis Tyner, Interview with Gene Kinn. WFOB, Fostoria, OH (14 min.) [CPA #203], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0689)
    - WBKC. Gus Hall and Jarvis Tyner, Interview. Chardon, OH [CPA #198], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0690)
    - Gus Hall - Tyner Campaign Committee. Gus Hall, on Jobs. Cleveland, OH [CPA #204], [1972/1976] (Box 22, Folder 132_0691)
    - WWTC. Jarvis Tyner, Interview with Paul Smith. Minneapolis, MN. [CPA #6], Jul 13, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 132_0692)
    - Gus Hall, Communist Candidate for President. 5 minutes. Southern. Tape 1 [CPA #147], Oct 19, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 132_0693)
    - WWRL. Jose Stevens T.H. Announcement #1. Harlem, New York, NY. Broadcast 11/2/72 [CPA #168], Oct 27, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 132_0694)
    - Jarvis Tyner, Radio Open and Close [CPA #172], Dec 17, 1973; Dec 21, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 132_0695)
    - Election Radio Program. Communist Party of Illinois. Tape 1 [CPA #7], Oct 29, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 132_0696)
    - Election Radio Program. Communist Party of Illinois. Tape 2 [CPA #8], Oct 29, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 132_0697)
    - Gus Hall, Open and Close (45 sec.) [CPA #149], Nov 25, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 132_0698)
    - Gus Hall, Open and Close / JarvisTyner, Open and Close / Gus Hall on U.S. Bicentennial [CPA #150], Aug 13, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 132_0699)
    - [KEBN] Mary Jane Odell Show. Gus Hall, Interview. Des Moines, IA / (KUNI). Gil Green, Address on Portugal and Communism. University of Northern Iowa, Cedar Fall, IA / (KUNI). Gil Green, Interview on Communist Party and its role... / NPR, All Things Considered. Excerpt on Smith Act [CPA #9], May 13, 1976; Nov 24, 1975; Dec 1975 (Box 23, Folder 132_0700)
    - KTLK. Robert Trujillo, Interview. CO [CPA #12], Jan 25, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 132_0701)
    - WQXR Daily World Talk. Gus Hall. (30 min.). Tape 1 [CPA #4], Mar 22, 1976; Mar 24, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 132_0702)
    - CBS. Gus Hall, on Bicentennial. (4 min.) [CPA #197], Jul 2, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 132_0703)
    - Gus Hall, Jarvis Tyner, and Hebert Aptheker. New York. Felt Forum Rally Promo [CPA #250], Oct 24, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 132_0704)
    - Two 60-sec. spots. Angela Davis - Gus Hall and Jarvis Tyner. New York, NY. [CPA #216], Nov 1976 (Box 23, Folder 132_0705)
    - Angela Davis and Gus Hall, Unidentified Radio Promo [CPA #201], [1980/1984] (Box 23, Folder 132_0706)
    - Gus Hall - Angela Davis Election Campaign. Angela Davis, on Jobs and the Lesser Evil [CPA #159], [1980/1984] (Box 23, Folder 132_0707)
    - WOWO. Gus Hall - Angela Davis Election Committee. Ft. Wayne, IN [CPA #811], [1980/1984] (Box 23, Folder 132_0708)
    - WNAR. "Take a Stand," 2 Spots. PA(?). [CPA #227], May 1980 (Box 23, Folder 132_0709)
    - Benjamin Davis (National Secretary, CP USA): WHDH Radio, Harvard Law School Forum. "The Communist Party and Constitutional Guarantees". Also on tape: Betty [Gannett or Smith]. Recorded at 1 7/8 [CPA #17], Mar 31, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 132_0710)
    - People before Profits (2 min. 12 sec.) [CPA #173], [1980s] (Box 23, Folder 132_0711)
    - #201 #3 1 [CPA #87], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0712)
    - #202 #1 1 [CPA #89], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0713)
    - Angela Davis for Daily World, New York, NY / Gus Hall. Pittsburgh, PA [CPA #99], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0714)
    - Angela Davis, PSA Rehearsal. Associated with CPA-997 [CPA #998], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0715)
    - Arnold Bechetti, and others. Spots (1 min.) [CPA #248], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0716)
    - Communist Party, USA, Questions and Answers [CPA #11], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0717)
    - Criley [sic]. Hearing at Federal Courthouse. Un-American Activities Committee, "Subversive Infiltration into Labor Unions." Chicago, IL [CPA #18], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0718)
    - Fred Hampton and T. Smothers [CPA #25], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0719)
    - Gus Hall and Jarvis Tyner [CPA #176], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0720)
    - WUPI. Gus Hall and Marvin Burak, American Communist Party Interview. Presque Isle, ME [CPA #932], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0721)
    - Gus Hall for WCLY, Cincinnati (30 min.) [CPA #16], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0722)
    - Gus Hall on Levine on FBI [CPA #15], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0723)
    - Gus Hall, on Racism and Women. Master (30 min.) [CPA #856], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0724)
    - Gus Hall Radio Program [CPA #951 A], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0725)
    - Gus Hall Radio Program [CPA #951 B], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0726)
    - Gus Hall Spot 1 ( 30 sec.) [CPA #49], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0727)
    - Gus Hall Spot 1 #1 (30 sec.) [CPA #80], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0728)
    - Gus Hall Spot #50(?) [CPA #139], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0729)
    - Gus Hall Spot #100 1 [CPA #131], undated (Box 23, Folder 132_0730)
    - Gus Hall Spot #101 1 [CPA #114], undated (Box 24, Folder 132_0731)
    - Gus Hall Spot #102 1 [CPA #137], undated (Box 24, Folder 132_0732)
    - Gus Hall Spot #103 1 [CPA #98], undated (Box 24, Folder 132_0733)
    - Gus Hall Spot #104 1 [CPA #95], undated (Box 24, Folder 132_0734)